Eric Du

Toronto, ON · ericxdu1@gmail.com · 647-822-0078

Professional Summary

Meticulous and detail oriented data administrator with extensive experience managing a variety of data sets. High level of computer proficiency and demonstrated ability to maintain exceptional attention to detail when handling high work loads to meet deadlines. Maintains accuracy and ability to pinpoint discrepancies when inputting data conveyed over the phone.

Work Experience

The Foot Clinic
Office Manager

Toronto, ON

September 2020 - Present

- Maintains a database of over 800 patients, 500 suppliers, 70 doctors/clinics and 50 different products.
- Accurately enters new patient information when onboarding over the phone and verifying when necessary.
- Accurately encodes products for tracking, ensures packages are ready for delivery and verifies all incoming products and invoices.
- Follows internal security procedures and backs up database to a hard copy twice daily.
- Reviews end of day settlement reports and ensures that all invoices, payment methods, cash deposits and accounts are balanced.

Q-Medical

Concord, ON

Accident Benefits Case Manager

Feburary 2019 - October 2019

- Managed and updated over 100 patient accounts, insurance claims and checked all source documents for accuracy, verifying when necessary.
- Developed and managed a digital client tracking system, converting all paper files and ensured that priorities and deadlines were met.
- Fostered positive relationships between clients, vendors and clinical teams by delivering timely responses to high volumes of written and verbal communication.
- Demonstrated strong knowledge of company products and services by providing alternative resources for ineligible clients.
- Responsible for all aspects of onboarding new clients including, conducting intake assessments, following up on all missing information and acting as a point of contact between clients, physicians and all relevant parties.

Total Recovery Rehab Centre

Toronto, ON

Physiotherapist/Administrative Assistant

December 2018 - January 2019

- Maintained confidentiality and a high level of customer service when handling sensitive information or emotional telephone calls.
- Accurately recorded daily patient attendance sheets, monitored remaining sessions and ensured all pending appointments were booked.
- Greeted all customers in a friendly manner, answered a multi-line phone provided information on company services and referred calls to the appropriate contact.
- Demonstrated strong communication and interpersonal skills in effectively resolving cusotmer complaints, resulting in increased customer loyalty.

SKILLS

Computer Literacy: Microsoft Office including advanced Excel, Universal, Filemaker, 70+ WPM

Languages: English, Mandarin

EDUCATION

University of Western Ontario